Guide to the Joseph Brodsky Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Restricted Fragile, 7.04; (16 boxes)
  - Box 168, folder 3730 (Box 224, Folder 4665)
  - Box 168, folder 3731 (Box 224, Folder 4666)
  - Box 168, folder 3732 (Box 224, Folder 4667)
  - Box 168, folder 3733 (Box 224, Folder 4668)
  - Box 168, folder 3734 (Box 224, Folder 4669)
  - Box 168, folder 3735 (Box 224, Folder 4670)
  - Box 168, folder 3736 (Box 224, Folder 4671)
  - Box 169, folder 3737 (Box 226, Folder 4701)
  - Box 169, folder 3738 (Box 226, Folder 4703)
  - Box 169, folder 3739 (Box 226, Folder 4698)
  - Box 169, folders 3740-3742 (Box 226, Folder 4695)
  - Box 169, folder 3743 (Box 226, Folder 4699)
  - Box 169, folder 3744-3745 (Box 226, Folder 4702)
  - Box 171, folder 3763
  - Box 171, folders 3767-3774
  - Box 172, folders 3774-3783
  - Box 173, folders 3784-3795
  - Box 174, folders 3796-3804
  - Box 175, folders 3805-3814
  - Box 176, folders 3815-3822
  - Box 188, folder 4074 (Box 234, Folder 4765)
  - Box 189, folder 4086 (Box 234, Folder 4766)
  - Box 189, folder 4114 (Box 234, Folder 4767)
  - Box 220, folders 4587-4604
  - Box 221, folders 4605-4622
  - Box 222, folders 4623-4640
  - Box 223, folders 4641-4658
  - Box 224, folders 4659-4675
  - Box 225, folders 4676-4683
  - Box 225, folders 4685-2690
  - Box 225, folders 4692-4694
  - Box 226, folder 4703
  - Box 232, folder 4759-4762
- Restricted Fragile Oversize, 11.36; (7 boxes)
  - Box 8, folder 212 (Box 235, Folder 4768)
  - Box 8, folders 221-226 (Box 235, Folder 4769)
  - Box 13, folders 348-360 (Box 235, Folder 4770)
  - Box 16, folder 429 (Box 235, Folder 4771)
  - Box 16, folders 431-433 (Box 235, Folder 4772)
  - Box 17, folder 450 (Box 235, Folder 4773)
  - Box 31, folders 682-693 (Box 235, Folder 4774)
  - Box 54, folder 941 (Box 236, Folder 4775)
  - Box 54, folder 955 (Box 236, Folder 4776)
  - Box 55, folder 975 (Box 236, Folder 4777)
  - Box 55, folders 983-984 (Box 236, Folder 4778)
  - Box 55, folder 992 (Box 236, Folder 4779)
  - Box 55, folder 1011 (Box 236, Folder 4780)
  - Box 55, folder 1031 (Box 236, Folder 4781)
  - Box 56, folders 1050-1054 (Box 236, Folder 4782)
  - Box 56, folder 1068 (Box 236, Folder 4783)
  - Box 56, folder 1071 (Box 236, Folder 4784)
  - Box 56, folder 1092 (Box 236, Folder 4785)
  - Box 56, folder 1093 (Box 236, Folder 4786)
  - Box 57, folder 1105 (Box 236, Folder 4787)
  - Box 57, folder 1120 (Box 236, Folder 4788)
  - Box 57 1136-1138 (Box 236, Folder 4789)
  - Box 59, folder 1215-1216 (Box 236, Folder 4790)
  - Box 60, folder 1226-1227 (Box 236, Folder 4791)
  - Box 60, folder 1271 (Box 236, Folder 4792)
  - Box 61, folder 1283 (Box 236, Folder 4793)
  - Box 61, folder 1285 (Box 236, Folder 4794)
  - Box 61, folder 1292 (Box 236, Folder 4795)
  - Box 62, folder 1370 (Box 236, Folder 4796)
  - Box 62, folder 1378 (Box 236, Folder 4797)
  - Box 63, folders 1458-1459 (Box 236, Folder 4798)
  - Box 64, folders 1493-1494 (Box 236, Folder 4799)
  - Box 64, folder 1523 (Box 236, Folder 4800)
  - Box 64, folder 1524 (Box 236, Folder 4801)
  - Box 64, folder 1498 (Box 236, Folder 4802)
  - Box 64, folder 1548 (Box 236, Folder 4803)
  - Box 65, folders 1579-1581 (Box 236, Folder 4804)
  - Box 65, folder 1625 (Box 236, Folder 4805)
  - Box 66, folders 1641-1642 (Box 236, Folder 4806)
  - Box 66, folders 1652-1653 (Box 236, Folder 4807)
  - Box 66, folders 1665-1667 (Box 236, Folder 4808)
  - Box 66, folder 1677 (Box 236, Folder 4809)
  - Box 66, folder 1678 (Box 236, Folder 4810)
  - Box 67, folders 1723-1726 (Box 236, Folder 4811)
  - Box 67, folder 1737 (Box 236, Folder 4812)
  - Box 68, folders 1760-1761 (Box 236, Folder 4813)
  - Box 77, folders 1893-1900 (Box 236, Folder 4814)
  - Box 77, folder 1907 (Box 236, Folder 4815)
  - Box 79, folders 1923-1924 (Box 236, Folder 4816)
  - Box 79, folder 1937 (Box 236, Folder 4817)
  - Box 79, folders 1940-1942 (Box 236, Folder 4818)
  - Box 81, folders 1983-1987 (Box 236, Folder 4819)
  - Box 83, folder 2000 (Box 236, Folder 4820)
  - Box 83, folders 2015-2018 (Box 236, Folder 4821)
  - Box 84, folders 2022-2028 (Box 236, Folder 4822)
  - Box 84, folders 2029-2030 (Box 236, Folder 4823)
  - Box 84, folder 2033 (Box 236, Folder 4824)
  - Box 197, folder 4290 (Box 236, Folder 4825)
  - Box 87, folder 2070 (Box 236, Folder 4826)
  - Box 88, folders 2097-2098 (Box 236, Folder 4827)
  - Box 89, folders 2129-2131 (Box 236, Folder 4828)
  - Box 89, folders 2132-2135 (Box 236, Folder 4829)
  - Box 90, folders 2160-2161 (Box 236, Folder 4829a)
  - Box 90, folders 2165-2167 (Box 236, Folder 4830)
  - Box 91, folder 2194 (Box 236, Folder 4831)
  - Box 91, folder 2197 (Box 236, Folder 4832)
  - Box 94, folder 2280 (Box 236, Folder 4833)
  - Box 94, folder 2285 (Box 236, Folder 4834)
  - Box 123, folder 2756 (Box 236, Folder 4835)
  - Box 123, folders 2781-2783 (Box 236, Folder 4836)
  - Box 54, folder 932 (Box 237, Folder 4837)
  - Box 54, folder 940 (Box 237, Folder 4838)
  - Box 54, folder 950 (Box 237, Folder 4839)
  - Box 59, folder 1200 (Box 237, Folder 4840)
  - Box 65, folder 1589 (Box 237, Folder 4841)
  - Box 77, folders 1904-1905 (Box 237, Folder 4842)
  - Box 77, folders 1909-1911 (Box 237, Folder 4843-4844)
  - Box 81, folder 1989 (Box 237, Folder 4845)
  - Box 81, folders 1990-1993 (Box 237, Folder 4846)
  - Box 83, folders 1995-1998 (Box 237, Folder 4847)
  - Box 90, folders 2152-2155 (Box 237, Folder 4848)
  - Box 91, folder 2177 (Box 237, Folder 4849)
  - Box 94, folder 2264 (Box 237, Folder 4850)
  - Box 94, folder 2268 (Box 237, Folder 4851)
  - Box 115, folder 2587 (Box 237, Folder 4852)
  - Box 177 and Oversize box 206 (Box 238, Folder 4853-4864)
  - Boxes 177-178 and Oversize boxes 206-207 (Box 239, Folder 4865-4878)
  - Box 178-179 and Oversize box 207 (Box 240, Folder 4879-4895)
  - Boxes 179-180 and Oversize box 207 (Box 241, Folder 4896-4910)
  - Box 192, folders 4222-4230 (Box 241, Folder 4911)